A Guide to the Secretary of the Board of Visitors, Office Administrative Files, 1959-1989
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Secretary of the Board of Visitors, Office Administrative Files 1959-1989
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-1/2/1.891
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
For ten years from the date of creation, access to these records will be granted only under the procedures of the Virginia Freedom of Information Act (Code of Virginia -2.1-340 ff.) or with the specific permission of the Secretary of the Board. Researchers interested in obtaining access to these records should direct a request in writing to the Office of the Legal Adviser, Madison Hall, University of Virginia.
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred to the library on 1989 July 10.
Contents List
- Association of Governing Boards 1971-1987, 2 folders (Box 1)
- Association of N.R.O.T.C. Colleges 1975-1986 (Box 1)
- Certifications 1967-1984, 3 folders (Box 1)
- Chapel Committee 1960-1984 (Box 1)
- Committee on Commencement and Convocations 1981-1985, 2 folders (Box 2)
- Docket, Preparation of 1967-1985, 2 folders (Box 2)
- Emergency Plan 1970-1982 (Box 2)
- Employee Relations 1972-1984 (Box 2)
- Board of Visitors' Memoranda 1986 Jan-Apr, 3 folders (Box 2)
- Miller, White Burkett 1970-1976 (Box 3)
- Minutes-Excerpts 1983-1984 (Box 3)
- Minutes, Correspondence 1980-1986, 2 folders (Box 3)
- Miscellaneous Names (A-Z) 1970-1987 (Box 3)
- Named Professorships 1988-1989, 3 folders (Box 3)
- Newsclips 1987-1988 (Box 3)
- Personal Items 1985-1986 (Box 4)
- Physical Plant, Department of 1979-1987 (Box 4)
- Planning Department 1970-1982 (Box 4)
- President's Staff Meeting Material 1987-1988, 4 folders (Box 4)
- Public Occasions Committee 1976-1980, 2 folders (Box 4)
- Rotunda-Correspondence 1981-1986, 2 folders (Box 5)
- Scholarships 1972-1973 (Box 5)
- School of Engineering and Applied Sciences 1969-1979 (Box 5)
- School of Law 1970-1983 (Box 5)
- Security File 1972-1977 (Box 5)
- The Seven Society 1969-1978 (Box 5)
- Shannon, Edgar, F. 1959-1988, 2 folders (Box 5)
- Student Publications 1969-1985 (Box 5)
- Vincent Shea 1969-1982 (Box 5)